<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-03T12:52:48.798-06:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2018-01-03T11:05:02.255-06:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/promolandingwithoutnav"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Delta Promotion"
        jcr:uuid="29916387-408e-4e4e-a271-ccffac14e0e1"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/promolandingwithoutnavpage"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <promoherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-07-27T08:23:50.174+05:30"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-03T12:52:48.793-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/promoherobanner"
                description="Get {{DELTAMILES}} BONUS MILES for enrolling + earn miles for every dollar you spend on your gas bill.*"
                displaylogo="true"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/delta-image.jpg"
                promocode="delta25"
                promoexpmsg="Start Earning! Offer ends {{expdate}}"
                textIsRich="true"
                title="Fuel for Your Next Getaway"/>
            <promotioncontent
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-07-27T10:17:02.253+05:30"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-03T11:04:41.244-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/promotioncontent"
                fineprinttext="&lt;p>*{{DELTAMILES}} bonus miles offer limited to qualified new customers who use 25,000 Ccf/2,500 Mcf per year or less enrolling on an eligible price plan by {{EXPIRATIONDATE}} using applicable promotion code. ONG service is available for eligible customers participating in the Choice program through their natural gas utility company. ONG rates do not include taxes or local utility charges. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call 1.866.466.4427, write to Ohio Natural Gas, PO Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit www.onlyong.com. Early termination charges apply for residential fixed price plans (12-Month plan: $150/$75; 6-Month plan: $75) and commercial fixed price plans (12-Month plan:  $300/$150; 6-Month plan: $150.) 30 days of continuous active gas service with ONG required to receive {{DELTAMILES}} bonus miles. Cannot be combined with any other offer. You must be a SkyMiles member and provide your SkyMiles account number to ONG to participate in this program and earn miles. In addition to bonus miles, two miles will be awarded for each dollar spent for ONG supplier gas charges for monthly gas service. Miles will not be awarded for taxes or one-time charges such as late fees. SkyMiles Medallion® Members will be awarded one additional mile for eligible charges. Miles will be posted to your SkyMiles account up to 4 weeks after each monthly bill date, provided you are an active customer of ONG and remain in good standing in the SkyMiles program. By enrolling in this program, you are authorizing the sharing of your information with Delta for the purpose of completing your enrollment and continuing your participation in the program. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev-ohio.macquarium.com:4502/content/onlyong/skymiles.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com/skymiles&lt;/a> for program terms and conditions. All SkyMiles program rules apply. To review the rules, please visit Membership Guide &amp;amp; Program Rules at &lt;a style=&quot;background-color: rgb(255,255,255);&quot; href=&quot;http://www.delta.com/memberguide&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.delta.com/memberguide&lt;/a>. All ONG program rules, and Delta prices and SkyMiles rules, are subject to change without notice. Taxes and fees for Award Travel are the responsibility of the passenger and must be paid at the time the ticket is booked. Award Travel seats are limited and may not be available on all flights or in all markets. Delta, SkyMiles, and the Delta logo are registered service marks of Delta Air Lines, Inc. Delta is not responsible for goods or services offered by any companies participating in miles promotions. Partner offers subject to the terms and conditions of each individual offer. See individual offers for details. Offers void where prohibited by law. Other restrictions may apply. Ohio Natural Gas and Delta Air Lines, Inc. are not affiliated, and neither has any obligation or liability with respect to the products or services to be provided by the other.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                heading="Choose from one of our plans to get started right away!"
                promoheadingline1="Choose from these"
                promoheadingline2="Fixed Rate Plans"
                text="&lt;h4>Get {{DELTAMILES}} bonus miles for signing up on an ONG fixed price plan, using applicable promo code, PLUS earn TWO miles for every dollar spent on your ONG supplier natural gas charges.*&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>And, if you are a SkyMiles Medallion® member, earn an additional mile for a total of THREE miles for each eligible dollar spent.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Don’t wait too long. Bonus miles offer ends {{EXPIRATIONDATE}}.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h5>Easy Sign Up&lt;/h5>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Switching is easy! One call to us and we will handle all of the details.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul style=&quot;list-style-position: inside;&quot;>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>There will be no service interruption.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Our experts ensure a seamless transition.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Your utility will continue to deliver your gas, send you one monthly bill and respond to service calls.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Limited to qualified new customers enrolled on an eligible price plan.*&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>For more program details, visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymiles.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com/skymiles&lt;/a>.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a title=&quot;frequently asked questions&quot; href=&quot;/content/onlyong/delta-faqs.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Frequently Asked Questions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymilesterms.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Delta Program Terms and Conditions&amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a title=&quot;Join Delta&quot; href=&quot;https://www.delta.com/profile/enrolllanding.action?mkcpgn=DP_ALL_DRCT_ALL_SP_150915_PRTNER17&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Join Delta Skymiles &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                textIsRich="[true,true,true]"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-02T15:40:18.873-05:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="josh"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
