<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-03-23T11:25:19.779-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2018-03-23T11:25:24.138-05:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/promolandingwithoutnav"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="CHOICE3V"
        jcr:uuid="8128caa3-4de5-4a26-a8b2-06e2fd3a3d25"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/promolandingwithoutnavpage"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <switchpromotionconte jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
            <promoherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2018-01-05T08:46:32.238-06:00"
                jcr:createdBy="penny"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-03-20T09:27:26.557-05:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/promoherobanner"
                displaylogo="true"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/promotions/ONG_VEDO_CHOICE3V_1568x348base.png"
                mobileimagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/promotions/ONG_VEDO_CHOICE3V_768x300.png"
                promoexpmsg="Hurry! Offer ends April 30, 2018!"
                textIsRich="true"
                title="&lt;p>Lock in Guaranteed Savings!&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"/>
            <applepromotionconten
                jcr:created="{Date}2018-01-08T08:45:49.236-06:00"
                jcr:createdBy="penny"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-03-23T11:25:19.776-05:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/applepromotioncontent"
                description="&lt;p>*Price and Visa Reward Card offers are available to new residential customers who use 1,500 Ccf per year or less, enrolling with Ohio Natural Gas between 3/20/2018 and 4/30/2018  using applicable promotion code; Visa Reward Card offer available only for such customers enrolling online at www.onlyong.com/CHOICE3V. ONG service is available for eligible customers participating in the Ohio Choice program through Vectren Energy Delivery of Ohio. ONG rates do not include taxes or local utility charges. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call 1.800.970.3146, write to Ohio Natural Gas, P.O. Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com&lt;/a>. For Variable Offer, ONG will guarantee a rate of at least $.05 per Ccf lower than the Standard Choice Offer (SCO) rate established each month by Vectren Energy Delivery of Ohio for your consumption billed through December 31, 2018; for each month during the term of this Variable Offer, customer will be charged the lesser of this guaranteed rate and ONG's Variable Plan at the standard price in effect at that time. Variable Offer price for March 2018 is $0.332/Ccf. Variable Offer price may change or remain the same each month, with no guaranteed savings. At any time, the customer may select another ONG plan without incurring an early termination charge. After December 31, 2018, customer will continue to receive service on a month-to-month basis on ONG's Variable Plan at the standard price in effect at that time. Customer must have continuous active service with Ohio Natural Gas for at least 60 days to be eligible to receive the Reward Card. After reaching eligibility, please allow 4-6 weeks for delivery. Visa Reward Card is issued by and is the property of CenterState Bank of Florida, NA pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. and is subject to the issuer's terms and conditions. Reward Cards will not have cash access and can be used everywhere Visa debit cards are accepted. All trademarks noted herein are held by their respective owners. Cannot be combined with any other offer. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                heading="Guaranteed to be at least 5¢ below the Standard Choice Offer (SCO) rate through 12/31/2018. Special Bonus: Enroll online and receive a {{giftCardValue | currency:&quot;$&quot;:0}} Visa® Reward Card!*"
                text=""
                textIsRich="true"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-15T08:49:28.111+05:30"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
