<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-01T11:57:40.309-06:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2018-01-01T11:57:44.560-06:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/referafriend"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Refer A Friend Authenticated"
        jcr:uuid="699542d7-5e62-4122-bbb3-01048b2cc5cb"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/referafriend"
        appid="388067291608116"
        hideInNav="true"
        ogdescription="Enroll with Ohio Natural Gas on their lowest available rates and we could each earn a $25 Visa Reward Card. It's that easy! Program Terms and conditions apply. #ad"
        ogimage="/raf25/assets/img/fb_share_image_25.jpg"
        oglocale="en_us"
        ogsitename="Ohio Natural Gas Refer-A-Friend"
        ogtitle="ONG's lowest available rate and $25!"
        ogtype="website"
        ogurl="/content/onlyong/promo-raf.html">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <staticherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-12-13T13:55:17.152-06:00"
                jcr:createdBy="penny"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-12-13T14:04:42.452-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/staticherobanner"
                description="Invite your friends to sign up with Ohio Natural Gas® on our lowest available rates and you’ll each receive a $25 Visa® Reward Card.* It’s that easy!"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/raf/hero.jpg"
                title="Refer a Friend"/>
            <raf_autenticated
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-15T09:16:53.996+05:30"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-01T11:57:40.302-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/raf-autenticated"
                awardterms="&lt;p>THE MAXIMUM AWARD UNDER THE RAF PROGRAM IS $500 IN VISA REWARD CARDS PER PERSON PER CALENDAR YEAR, UNLESS SPECIFICALLY AUTHORIZED BY Ohio Natural Gas IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION. This $500 limit applies to the total of all Ohio Natural Gas Visa Reward Card promotional offers received. Including but not limited to the Refer-a-Friend Program. To see the full Refer-a-Friend program terms and conditions &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/termsandconditions.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>click here&lt;/a>.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                benefits="&lt;h4> &lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h4>Here are the benefits of the program&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul style=&quot;list-style-position: inside;&quot;>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>You share the ONG experience with a friend.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>For each friend who enrolls, you can each get a $25 Visa® Reward Card.*&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>The more you share, the more you can earn!*&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i> &lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                bodyofthankyou="If your email address is on file with us, you will receive an email when a friend enrolls with your Referral Code."
                changeemailmsg="&lt;p>By changing your email here, you will change the email address associated with all of your ONG notifications. If you'd prefer to use a different address to send your referral emails, you can do so after clicking &amp;quot;Send Email&amp;quot; on the next screen.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                companylogoinemail="/content/dam/ohgre/raf/ReferAFriend_Stack_4C_ONG.png"
                emailbodyplaceholder="I'm very happy with my service from Ohio Natural Gas, and I think you will be too. If you sign up with ONG using the referral and promotion codes below, we can both get a $25 Visa Reward Card. Not bad, huh?"
                facebook="/content/dam/ohgre/socialsharing/facebook@3x.png"
                helppagelinks="&lt;p>To find out more about the Refer-a-Friend program: &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/gre/raf-faqs.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a>&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/termsandconditions.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>RAF Program Terms and Conditions&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                popupfootercontactinfo="&lt;h4>Customer Service&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>1.888.466.4427&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;8 a.m. – 5 p.m. ET Monday – Friday&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                popupfootercontent="&lt;p>The is a post-only message from Ohio Natural Gas. Please do not attempt to reply to this message. We would love to hear from you if you have questions. For assistance with your account, please contact us via phone or by e-mail at customerservice@onlyong.com&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                rafemailbody="&lt;p>Enrolling is easy. Either click the button below to enroll online, or give ONG a call at 1.888.466.4427 and provide the Referral Code and Promotion Code below. Your gas service won't be interrupted when you switch. Ohio Natural Gas experts will handle all the details for you.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                rafemailsubject="Enroll with Ohio Natural Gas and we could both get $25!"
                raflogoinemail="/content/dam/ohgre/raf/raf-logo.png"
                rafpromocode="RAF25"
                rafterms="&lt;p>* Subject to the Refer-a-Friend program (“RAF Program”) rules and &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/termsandconditions.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>terms and conditions&lt;/a>. Offer limited to: (i) qualified new residential/commercial customers (each a “Referee”) who use a promotion code through this RAF Program to enroll in an eligible ONG price plan (each a “RAF Referee”), and (ii) existing customers who refer one or more Referees using the RAF Program (each a “Referrer”). Referrers may earn a $25&amp;nbsp;Visa® Reward Card for each Referee who: (i) enrolls on an eligible ONG price plan, (ii) provides Referrer’s Referral Code at enrollment, and (iii) begins burning gas on an eligible ONG price plan. Referrers must: have either an active or pending account with ONG when Referee begins burning gas; authenticate their ONG account; accept the RAF Program terms and conditions; and participate by using the communication methods provided (email, Facebook, and Twitter) at &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/promo-raf.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com/promo-raf&lt;/a> and as specified in the RAF Program terms and conditions. RAF Referees earn a $25 Visa Reward Card by: (i) enrolling in an eligible ONG price plan, (ii) providing the RAF Program promotion code at enrollment (and may enter their Referrer’s unique Referral Code at that time), and (iii) reaching 60 days of continuous active service with ONG on such eligible price plan. Allow 4-6 weeks for delivery. Maximum award: $500 in Visa Reward Cards per person / calendar year for all ONG Visa Reward Card promotional offers. Offer valid for qualifying enrollments processed by ONG between 12/01/2017 and 06/30/2018. ONG service is available for eligible customers participating in the Choice program through their natural gas utility company. ONG rates do not include taxes or local utility charges. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call 1.888.466.4427, write to Ohio Natural Gas, PO Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.onlyong.com&lt;/a>. RAF Referees cannot combine this offer with any other offer but may provide the Referrer’s unique Referral Code when enrolling using another ONG promotional offer. Referrers may combine this offer with their pre-existing discounts and promotions. The Visa Reward Card is issued by and is the property of CenterState Bank of Florida, NA pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. and is subject to the issuer’s terms and conditions. Reward Cards will not have cash access and can be used everywhere Visa debit cards are accepted. All trademarks noted herein are held by their respective owners. © 2017 Ohio Natural Gas. All Rights Reserved.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                referralamount="$25*"
                referralcode="Your unique Referral Code is"
                sharebyemail="&lt;h4>Share by Email&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Send a customized email to your friends. This email contains all the information your friends need to enroll with ONG using your Referral Code.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                sharesocially="&lt;h4>Share Socially&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Click the icons below to share this offer with your friends through your favorite social networks. If they enroll with ONG, you could both earn a $25 Visa&lt;sup>®&lt;/sup> Reward Card.*&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                subheader="&lt;p>Tell your friends to enroll with Ohio Natural Gas by going online to &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/promo-raf1.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.onlyong.com/RAF25 &lt;/a>or calling &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-888-466-4427&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1.888.466.4427&lt;/a>. In order for you both to be eligible for the $25 Visa&lt;sup>®&lt;/sup> Reward Card, your friend must provide Promotion Code RAF25 and your Referral Code {{customerInfo.custID}} at the time he or she enrolls.*&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                textIsRich="[true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true]"
                thankyouheader="Thank you for referring your friends to Ohio Natural Gas!"
                twitter="/content/dam/ohgre/socialsharing/twitter@3x.png"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-15T01:27:49.830-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
