<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-10T13:14:17.488-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/helppage"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Privacy Policy"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/helppage"
        hideInNav="true"
        portalname="Select Portal name">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <staticherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-10T11:58:12.570-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-10T11:58:53.287-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/staticherobanner"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/hero-image.jpg"
                title="Privacy Policy"/>
            <terms_landing
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-10T11:58:57.830-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-10T13:14:17.481-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/terms-landing"
                description="&lt;p>SouthStar Energy Services LLC (&amp;quot;SouthStar&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;we&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;us&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;our&amp;quot;) respects your privacy and is committed to complying with this privacy policy (&amp;quot;Privacy Policy&amp;quot;), which describes what information we collect about you, including how we collect it, how we use it, with whom we may share it and what choices you have regarding our use of your information. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected on our websites, which include, but are not limited to, southstarenergy.com, gng.com, gngsavings.com, guaranteedbill.com, www.newjerseyenergy.com, trueblueschools.com, gngconnections.com, sseenrollment.com, onlygng.com, onlyfng.com, grandrapidsenergy.com, marylandenergy.com, newyorknatgas.com, nicorsolutions.com, nicoradvancedenergy.com, onlyong.com and gnggivesback.com (each, individually, a &amp;quot;Website&amp;quot; and, collectively, the &amp;quot;Websites&amp;quot;), any mobile applications associated with these Websites (the &amp;quot;Mobile Applications&amp;quot;), all interactive features, applications, widgets, blogs, social networks and social network &amp;quot;tabs&amp;quot;, and other online or wireless offerings that post a link to this Privacy Policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology or any associated content, material, or functionality contained on the Websites or Mobile Applications (collectively, the &amp;quot;Services&amp;quot; and, together with the Website and the Mobile Applications, the &amp;quot;System&amp;quot;). SouthStar operates as a natural gas marketer under the names &amp;quot;SouthStar Energy Services&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Georgia Natural Gas&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Ohio Natural Gas&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Maryland Energy&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Florida Natural Gas&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Grand Rapids Energy&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;New York Natural Gas&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;New Jersey Energy&amp;quot;. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, references to &amp;quot;SouthStar&amp;quot; shall include SouthStar Energy Services LLC and all of its members, affiliates, subsidiaries (Prairie Point Energy, L.L.C. d/b/a Nicor Advanced Energy LLC and Nicor Solutions, L.L.C.), directors, officers, agents, and employees.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is a part of the terms of use of the System located here (the &amp;quot;Terms of Use&amp;quot;). We encourage you to become familiar with the terms and conditions of both this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. By accessing and using the System, or any part thereof, you agree that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy, and that in exchange for access to the System, you accept and consent to the privacy practices (and any uses and disclosures of information about you) that are described in this Privacy Policy.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                heading="Overview"
                termslist="[{&quot;termstitle&quot;:&quot;What Information Do We Collect?&quot;\,&quot;termsdescription&quot;:&quot;&lt;p>As described in detail below\, we may collect certain identifying information from or about you in connection with your use of\, or your submissions to\, the System (collectively\, the &amp;quot;Collected Information&amp;quot;). Collected Information may include identifying information provided to the System on your behalf by one of our call center employees when you call our call centers to make a payment or enroll in one of our products or services. Collected Information includes\, without limitation\, any information that may be used to identify an individual\, including\, but not limited to\, a first and last name\, a home\, business\, service or other physical address\, geographic location\, business name\, a phone number\, a Social Security number\, an email address\, tax identification number\, employer name\, employer information (i.e.\, company size\, industry\, number of employees)\, utility account number or other identifier\, credit or debit card number (and related information such as expiration date)\, bank account information\, and account number or other identifier used in connection with our marketing alliances (e.g.\, your Delta SkyMiles number pursuant to our alliance with Delta). SouthStar uses the information we collect to provide natural gas and other products and services to you; to provide required regulatory communications to you; to open\, maintain\, and close accounts; for payment processing; for marketing activities; for fulfillment; for provision of quotes and other pricing information; to improve the System&amp;#39;s content\, materials\, and services; and to more effectively and efficiently respond to both current and future customer inquiries.&lt;br>\\n&lt;br>\\nSome of our promotional offers have a refer-a-friend feature that allows you to have the offer sent to a friend with your comment. If you choose to use this feature\, we may collect and use the email address of your friend(s) to facilitate the referral but do not store it for other uses. If your friend becomes a customer of ours\, we may tell you or otherwise make that information available to you.&lt;br>\\n&lt;/p>\\n&quot;},{&quot;termstitle&quot;:&quot;Cookies and Usage Reports&quot;\,&quot;termsdescription&quot;:&quot;&lt;p>By placing a small file known as a &amp;quot;cookie&amp;quot; on your computer (or other device)\, SouthStar&amp;#39;s\, and its third party service providers\, servers passively gather information about all visitors use of the System for several reasons\, including\, but not limited to\, the following: statistics collection and analysis\, System optimization\, analytics (as described below)\, market research\, and maintenance of user login information. The information that we and our third party service providers track with cookies includes\, but is not limited to\, the type of browser (such as Google Chrome or Internet Explorer) and Internet-connected device being used to access the System\, your Internet protocol (&amp;quot;IP&amp;quot;) address\, your home domain or Internet service provider\, your referrer URL (which is the URL for the website that you were viewing prior to visiting the System)\, how you were directed to the System\, which specific pages you access on the System\, how long you view each page\, the time and date you access our System and the total number of visitors to the System and any portions thereof. We use your IP address to determine the general physical location of your computer or device and understand from what geographic locations our System visitors come.&lt;br>\\n&lt;br>\\nWe\, and/or our third party service providers\, may place cookies or similar files on your computer for security purposes (such as authentication)\, to facilitate site navigation and to personalize your experience while visiting our Website. Cookies allow us and our third party service providers to collect technical and navigational information\, such as browser type\, time spent on our Website and pages visited (these types of cookies are typically referred to as &amp;quot;Session Cookies&amp;quot;).&lt;br>\\n&lt;br>\\nOur third party service providers use pixels which cause &amp;quot;cookies&amp;quot; or similar technology to be stored on your browsers when you visit the System. This is necessary for our third party service providers to provide retargeting services. The collection of this anonymous data allows us to better target our advertising to your interests. The data also helps us and our third party service providers improve our respective product and services.&lt;br>\\n&lt;br>\\nMost popular Internet browser applications will allow you to configure the browser so as not to accept cookies. However\, setting your browser to reject cookies may\, in certain instances\, prevent you from taking full advantage of the System (or some portion thereof) and its capabilities\, or cause some features of the System to function improperly or more slowly.&lt;br>\\n&lt;br>\\nThe Websites (and certain other portions of the System) use Google Analytics (including the Universal Analytics feature)\, a web analysis service provided by Google\, in order to better understand your use of our Websites (or other portions of the System) and how we can improve the Websites and the System. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit a Website\, what pages they visit when they do so\, and what other websites they used prior to coming to such Website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Websites\, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your personal information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit a Website\, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google&amp;#39;s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Websites or the System is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the System\, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected on the System to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. To more fully understand how Google may use the data it collects on the System\, please review &amp;quot;How Google uses data when you use our partners sites or apps&amp;quot;\, (located here or any successor URL). If you would like additional information regarding the security and privacy practices of Google&amp;#39;s Universal Analytics feature\, please review the materials provided by Google here.&lt;br>\\n&lt;br>\\nSome of the areas of the System may contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow SouthStar\, and its third party providers\, to count and track users who have visited certain portions of the System. Web beacons collect only limited information\, including a cookie number\, time and date of a page view\, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. Web beacons do not collect any of your personal information.&lt;/p>\\n&quot;}]"
                textIsRich="true"/>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
