<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-11T11:42:09.979-06:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="josh"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2018-01-10T14:44:41.273-06:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/enrollpage"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Customer Lookup"
        jcr:uuid="bf3fd662-5ca1-4a61-8f70-61ee3555fd98"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/enrollpage"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <enroll_customer
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-17T08:23:33.475+05:30"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-11T11:42:09.971-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="josh"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/enroll-customer"
                acceptspecialoffer="Yes, Ohio Natural Gas may send me information about special offers from Ohio Natural Gas and its marketing partners."
                acceptterms="&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;b>Terms and Conditions of Service  &lt;/b>&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;b>November 2016&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>By receiving or continuing to receive service from Ohio Natural Gas&lt;sup>SM&lt;/sup> (ONG), you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of service as set forth below, including provisions regarding Binding Arbitration, and in your welcome letter and other enrollment correspondence (collectively, your “contract”).&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Natural Gas Service&lt;/b> – You must be at least 18 years old or an emancipated minor to establish an account with ONG.  After your successful enrollment with ONG and confirmation by the utility, ONG will supply your natural gas until either you or ONG cancels your service. Your service with ONG begins on the date provided to you by the utility. Within 3 business days of receiving your enrollment request, ONG will submit your request to the utility. ONG is not responsible for utility delays in processing your enrollment or cancellation request.  This contract governs your pricing with ONG during the term of your contract, but the timing of application of those prices to your utility bill may be impacted by the timing of your utility meter read cycles.  In addition, because meter read cycles may differ from the start and end dates of your fixed price or Guaranteed Bill&lt;sup>SM&lt;/sup> plan contract, you may not receive the same number of bills as the number of months in your contract with ONG. The utility will deliver the natural gas you purchase from ONG to your premises, read your meter, provide emergency services, and issue your bill each month. The utility will charge you separately for those services. ONG’s charges for natural gas will appear as a separate line item on your bill. Sales tax will appear separately.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>For new customers, your contract begins on your effective date as established by the utility and continues for the period specified in your welcome letter. For existing ONG customers choosing a new price plan, your contract is effective upon the date your price plan change request is processed by ONG, and continues for the length of your contract, unless a later effective date is determined between you and ONG (e.g., if you are on a current fixed price or Guaranteed Bill plan contract with ONG and you request a new fixed, Guaranteed Bill or variable plan contract with ONG, it will generally take effect the day following the expiration of your current fixed price or Guaranteed Bill plan contract).&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>ONG Price Plans&lt;/b> – Your price plan, per unit price, as applicable if you have selected a fixed or variable plan, and Guaranteed Bill amount, as applicable if you have a selected a Guaranteed Bill plan, are specified in your welcome letter.  ONG’s price plans fall into three categories: variable, fixed and Guaranteed Bill. ONG offers residential pricing for residential customers and commercial pricing for commercial customers.  ONG may from time to time offer promotional or discounted prices.  Sales tax and utility charges are not included in the price per Mcf or Ccf, whichever is applicable based on your utility, or Guaranteed Bill amount.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>ONG Variable Plans&lt;/b>: With an ONG variable plan, your price per unit of natural gas may change or remain the same from month to month based on market conditions. Service under a variable plan is on a month-to-month contract basis until cancelled by you or ONG. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Many factors influence retail natural gas pricing, including wholesale gas costs, which are impacted by the weather; general market conditions; transportation costs; operating expenses; and other factors. ONG sets its prices each month based on the most current information available, including, but not limited to, the NYMEX monthly contract price for that month. ONG cannot predict the volatility of the market or what its customers will pay for gas in the future. Under a variable plan, you may switch to another ONG price plan for which you qualify at any time at no additional charge. The per-unit price on a variable plan may be higher or lower than on a fixed plan.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>ONG Fixed Plans&lt;/b>: With a fixed price plan, ONG charges you a fixed price per unit during the term of the contract. This contract governs your pricing with ONG during the term of your contract, but the timing of application of those prices to your utility bill may be impacted by the timing of your utility meter read cycles.  In addition, because meter read cycles may differ from the start and end dates of your fixed price plan contract, you may not receive the same number of bills as the number of months in your contract with ONG.  When you select a fixed price plan, you commit to remain with ONG at the same price for the term of your contract. If Dominion East Ohio or Vectren Energy Delivery of Ohio is your utility, you commit to remain with ONG at the same price for the term of your contract if you move within the utility’s service area.  Although ONG’s currently available fixed price may change at any time, the price for the term of your contract will be ONG’s fixed price in effect at the time you selected your fixed plan. The per-unit price on a fixed plan may be higher or lower than on a variable plan.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>ONG Guaranteed Bill Plans (Columbia Gas of Ohio only):&lt;/b>  With a Guaranteed Bill plan, ONG charges you a flat bill amount (the Guaranteed Bill amount) for your natural gas consumption for each standard service period during the term of the contract.  A standard service period is a 27 – 34 day meter reading cycle.  In some instances, there could be a non-standard service period – for example, while establishing or terminating service with ONG.  In the event you experience a service period that is longer or shorter than a standard service period, your Guaranteed Bill amount will be prorated.  This prorated amount will be calculated by dividing your Guaranteed Bill amount by 30 days, and multiplying that number by the number of days in the applicable service period.    Further, this contract governs your pricing with ONG during the term of your contract, but the timing of application of those prices to your utility bill may be impacted by the timing of your utility meter read cycles.  In addition, because meter read cycles may differ from the start and end dates of your Guaranteed Bill plan contract, you may not receive the same number of bills as the number of months in your contract with ONG.  Your Guaranteed Bill amount includes all natural gas commodity costs but does not include sales tax, utility charges or one-time charges such as late fees.  When you select a Guaranteed Bill plan, you commit to remain with ONG at the same Guaranteed Bill amount for the term of your contract. Guaranteed Bill plan contracts are not transferrable between customers or premises.  The total bill amount on a Guaranteed Bill plan may be higher or lower than the total bill amount on a variable plan or fixed plan.  ONG reserves the right to limit enrollments or re-enrollments on a Guaranteed Bill plan at its sole discretion.  ONG also reserves the right to limit the availability of a Guaranteed Bill plan to certain customers based on a number of factors not prohibited by applicable law, including but not limited to a customer’s action to terminate any prior contract with ONG prior to the end of its established term, credit criteria, payment history, consumption history and age of premises.   &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Contract Renewal Provisions for Fixed Price and Guaranteed Bill Plans - This contract will automatically renew on a month-to-month basis on ONG’s Variable Plan at the standard price in effect at that time, unless ONG provides you with notice, as set forth below, that the contract will renew for a longer term at a fixed price or Guaranteed Bill amount. ONG will send at least one and may send you up to two notices offering to renew this contract under the same or different terms and conditions, including the applicable early termination charge, if any, and the new fixed price or Guaranteed Bill amount, if applicable.  If the contract will renew at a fixed price or Guaranteed Bill plan and for a longer term than month to month, you will receive the first notice by mail at least forty-five (45) and not more than ninety (90) days prior to the expiration of this contract and the second notice, if applicable, no less than thirty-five (35) days prior to the expiration date of this contract.  This contract shall automatically renew in accordance with the terms and conditions indicated in the notices unless you notify ONG between the time of receipt of notice and the expiration of your current contract.  You can also call ONG during that time period to request a new fixed or variable plan contract, or, if eligible at the time of the request, a Guaranteed Bill plan contract, to take effect the day following the expiration of your current fixed price or Guaranteed Bill plan contract. If you again select a fixed price plan, you will receive the fixed price in effect when you contact ONG and make your selection. If you again select a Guaranteed Bill plan, if eligible at the time of the request, you will receive the Guaranteed Bill amount quoted when you contact ONG and make your selection.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>If you cancel your contract after receiving such notice but prior to the effective date of automatic renewal, you will be obligated under this contract until the end of the then-current term. If you do terminate this contract and do not initiate another contract with ONG, you can choose another gas supplier or, if you do not choose another gas supplier, you will return to the utility for service.  If you decide not to renew your contract with ONG, whether you select another plan with us, return your natural gas service to the utility or choose another natural gas supplier, in order to avoid an early termination charge on your current contract, please be sure any actions that you take become effective after your current contract expires.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>ONG Early Termination Charges&lt;/b> –&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b> &lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>12 Month Fixed Price Plan:&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If you terminate your plan during the initial term of your contract, except as specifically set forth in your ONG contract at the time of enrollment, ONG will assess you an early termination charge of $150 for residential customers or $300 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan more than six months prior to its scheduled expiration date, or $75 for residential customers or $150 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan six months or less prior to its scheduled expiration date.  Such charge is intended to compensate ONG for losses and expenses it estimates it will incur as the result of the early termination of a customer’s fixed price plan.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>6 Month Fixed Price Plan or Winter Fixed Price Plan:&lt;/b>&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If you terminate your plan during the initial term of your contract, except as specifically set forth in your ONG contract at the time of enrollment, ONG will assess you an early termination charge of $75 for residential customers or $150 for commercial customers.  Such charge is intended to compensate ONG for losses and expenses it estimates it will incur as the result of the early termination of a customer’s fixed price plan.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>10 Month Fixed Price Plan:&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If you terminate your plan during the initial term of your contract, except as specifically set forth in your ONG contract at the time of enrollment, ONG will assess you an early termination charge of $125 for residential customers or $250 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan during the first four months of the plan, or $75 for residential customers or $150 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan six months or less prior to its scheduled expiration date.  Such charge is intended to compensate ONG for losses and expenses it estimates it will incur as the result of the early termination of a customer’s fixed price plan.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>12 Month Guaranteed Bill Plan:&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If you terminate your plan during the initial term of your contract, except as specifically set forth in your ONG contract at the time of enrollment, and you enroll in the Guaranteed Bill Plan between January 1&lt;sup>st&lt;/sup> and June 30&lt;sup>th&lt;/sup>, ONG will assess you an early termination charge of $100 for residential customers or $200 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan more than six months prior to its scheduled expiration date, or $50 for residential customers or $100 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan six months or less prior to its scheduled expiration date.  If you terminate your plan during the initial term of your contract, except as specifically set forth in your ONG contract at the time of enrollment, and you enroll in the Guaranteed Bill Plan between July 1&lt;sup>st&lt;/sup> and December 31&lt;sup>st&lt;/sup>, ONG will assess you an early termination charge of $150 for residential customers or $300 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan more than six months prior to its scheduled expiration date, or $100 for residential customers or $200 for commercial customers if you terminate your plan six months or less prior to its scheduled expiration date.  Such charge is intended to compensate ONG for losses and expenses it estimates it will incur as the result of the early termination of a customer’s Guaranteed Bill plan.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Billing/Collections&lt;/b> – Based on your price plan, your ONG gas charges will be billed by the utility, along with the utility’s charges for its services. By agreeing to these terms and conditions of service, you agree to pay ONG charges in accordance with the utility’s payment procedures. If you do not pay your bills in accordance with those payment procedures or if you fail to comply with any agreed-upon payment arrangement, then the utility’s service may be terminated in accordance with the utility’s tariffs, and this contract may be cancelled. If that occurs, you are required to pay the balance owed, including any early termination charges.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>ONG reserves the right to bill you directly for our services, and if that occurs, we may complete a credit check and (at our sole discretion) require a security deposit. ONG and the utility are responsible for collecting amounts owed on their respective bills. Upon 14 days’ written notice, ONG may cancel this contract for nonpayment. In that event, you must pay the entire ONG balance due, including any early termination charges.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Customer Service/Dispute Procedures&lt;/b> – ONG is not responsible for resolving disputes with the utility. However, if you have questions concerning your ONG service, you may call ONG toll-free at 1-888-466-4427 Monday-Friday from 8 a.m. to 5 p.m. EST, excluding national holidays. You also may contact us by mail at P.O. Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or by e-mail at customerservice@onlyong.com. In the event of a dispute with ONG, you first should contact an ONG customer service representative within 30 days of receipt of your bill. If your complaint is not resolved, you may contact our Customer Care Center and ask for an ONG customer service supervisor. If your complaint is not resolved after you have called ONG, or for general utility information, residential and business customers may contact the public utilities commission of Ohio (PUCO or Commission) for assistance at 1-800-686-7826 (toll free) from eight a.m. to five p.m. weekdays, or at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.puco.ohio.gov&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>http://www.puco.ohio.gov&lt;/a>.  Hearing or speech impaired customers may contact the PUCO via 7-1-1 (Ohio relay service).  The Ohio consumers’ counsel (OCC) represents residential utility customers in matters before the PUCO.  The OCC can be contacted at 1-877-742-5622 (toll free) from eight a.m. to five p.m. weekdays, or at http://www.pickocc.org.   &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>If you need to report a natural gas leak or emergency, call the utility at the number listed on your bill.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Right of Rescission&lt;/b>– If you are a new ONG customer, the utility will send you a letter confirming your ONG enrollment. You may rescind your enrollment without penalty within 7 business days of the postmark date of that letter by contacting the utility by phone (Columbia Gas of Ohio:  1-800-344-4077; Duke Energy:  1-800-544-6900; Vectren Energy Delivery of Ohio:  1-800-227-1376; Dominion East Ohio:  1-800-362-7557) or in writing.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Contract Cancellation/Termination&lt;/b> - You may cancel a variable plan at any time without an early termination charge. If you cancel a fixed price or Guaranteed Bill plan prior to the end of the contract term, early termination charges will apply, as described in “ONG Early Termination Charges” above. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>This contract will terminate automatically if the utility does not serve the requested premises, if you move (other than as specified below), or if ONG returns you to the utility’s service. You have the right to terminate this contract without penalty if you move to a new location outside of your utility service area.  You must notify ONG if you are moving to a new location outside of your utility service area in order to have your early termination charge credited back to you. If Dominion East Ohio or Vectren Energy Delivery of Ohio is your utility and you move inside the utility’s service area, ONG will continue service at the new location, and you automatically grant the utility the right to forward your new service address to ONG.  If Columbia Gas of Ohio or Duke Energy is your utility, you have the right to terminate this contract without penalty if you move to a new location inside your utility service area.  Under these circumstances, you must notify ONG in order to have your early termination charge credited back to you.  However, ONG can provide service at the new location under a new contract if you notify ONG at the time of your move and establish service with the utility at the new location with ONG as your service provider.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Termination typically is effective with the next full utility billing cycle that occurs after the utility is notified of the request to terminate service.  You are responsible for all fees and charges until your service is terminated.  If you change to another natural gas provider (including the utility), the utility may assess a switching fee under its tariff and ONG reserves the right to assess a switching fee.  If you return to the utility for service, then you may be charged a price other than the utility’s applicable tariff rate.  The Binding Arbitration provisions of this contract shall survive termination of this contract or of your gas service.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Your Account/Contact Information/ Call Monitoring&lt;/b> – You have the right to request (without charge) up to 24 months of payment history for your ONG service. Additional payment history is available for a fee.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Other than for operation, maintenance, assignment and transfer of your account, or for commercial collection, percentage of income payment plan aggregation, and governmental aggregation, ONG will not disclose your account number without your written consent or pursuant to a court order or Commission order. Other than for credit checking and credit reporting, ONG will not release your social security number without your written consent to do so or pursuant to a court order. Under this contract, you are allowing the utility to provide ONG information about your account, including meter readings and historical data.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>By providing your contact information to ONG (name, address, telephone number, fax number, e-mail address, etc.), you acknowledge that you are consenting to be contacted by mail, telephone, fax, voicemail, or e-mail by ONG, a third party on behalf of ONG, or an associated company. ONG may monitor and record telephone calls to our Customer Care Center for quality assurance purposes. All calls for new service are recorded in compliance with Commission guidelines.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Regulatory Changes &lt;/b>– This contract is subject to present and future legislation, orders, rules, regulations and decisions of any duly constituted governmental authority having jurisdiction over this contract or the services to be provided hereunder.  If at some future date there is a change in any law, rule, regulation or pricing structure whereby ONG is prevented, prohibited or frustrated from carrying out the terms of this contract, then at its sole discretion ONG shall have the right to cancel this contract on 15 days’ notice to you.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Extraordinary Events&lt;/b> – If an event occurs that delays or makes it impossible for ONG to perform, such as an act of God, extraordinary weather occurrence, a facility outage on the utility system or interstate pipeline systems, a failure to perform by the utility, war, civil disturbance, or national emergency, our performance under these terms and conditions shall be excused for the duration of the event. Under such conditions, ONG may elect to discontinue service immediately, without notice.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Assignment&lt;/b> – ONG reserves the right to assign this contract to another natural gas supplier approved by the PUCO. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Limitation of Liability and Disclaimer of Warranty – ONG is not responsible for any losses or damages resulting from any actions or policies of, or associated with, the utility, including interruption of service, termination of service, defective service, or operation and maintenance of the utility’s system, nor is ONG responsible for damages sought because of in-home or building damage. The remedy in any claim by you against ONG will be solely limited to direct actual damages. All other remedies at law or in equity are hereby waived by you. In no event will either ONG or you be liable for consequential, incidental, indirect, special, or punitive damages. These limitations apply without regard to the cause of any liability or damages. There are no third-party beneficiaries to this contract.  ONG makes no representations or warranties other than those expressly set forth herein, and ONG expressly disclaims all other warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, merchantability and fitness for a particular use.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Binding Arbitration &lt;/b>–&lt;b> You and ONG agree that any and all disputes, controversies and claims (“Dispute(s)”) arising out of or related to this contract or to your gas service from ONG that cannot be resolved through the Customer Service/Dispute Procedures described above will be resolved through binding arbitration by the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”).&lt;/b> Arbitration means that you and ONG will have a fair hearing before a neutral arbitrator instead of in a court with a judge or jury, except for certain small claims discussed below. The decision of the arbitrator will be final and binding, and the arbitrator’s award may be confirmed and entered as a judgment by any court of competent jurisdiction.  For commercial customers the arbitration will be governed by the AAA Commercial Arbitration Rules, except as modified by these Terms and Conditions of Service.  For residential customers the arbitration will be governed by the AAA Consumer Arbitration Rules, except as modified by these Terms and Conditions of Service.    &lt;b>Nothing in this section limits your right to file a complaint with the Public Utilities Commission of Ohio (PUCO).&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>You can initiate arbitration by filing a &lt;a href=&quot;/content/dam/ohgre/termsandconditions/Ohio/AAA-claim_form.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Claim Form&lt;/a> with the AAA and by sending a copy of the Claim Form to ONG at P.O. Box 14657, Cleveland, Ohio 44114.  The Claim Form is available on the AAA website, www.adr.org, on the ONG website, www.onlyong.com, or by calling ONG at 1-888-466-4427.  You can complete the Claim Form on the AAA website or you can mail the Claim Form to AAA Case Filing Services, 1101 Laurel Oak Road, Suite 100, Voorhees, New Jersey 08043, with a copy to ONG. You do not need to send payment to the AAA, ONG will pay the filing fee upon receipt of a copy of the Claim Form.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The arbitration will be conducted by a single arbitrator who shall be mutually agreed upon by the parties; provided, however, that if the parties are unable to agree then the arbitrator shall be selected by the AAA in accord with its rules. The arbitration will take place in the county where you are billed or in a mutually agreed location. If the amount of the claim is $25,000 or less, you may choose whether the arbitration takes place in person, by telephone, or on written submissions. If the amount of the claim is more than $25,000, the type of hearing shall be determined by the applicable AAA rules. The arbitrator will make his/her decision in writing, but need not provide a statement of reasons unless requested by either party, in which event the arbitrator will provide a concise statement of the essential findings and conclusions on which the award is based.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>ONG will pay all arbitration filing fees and arbitrator’s costs. You are responsible for all additional costs that you incur in the arbitration, including, but not limited to, attorney’s fees (if you choose to be represented by an attorney) and expert witness fees. You shall not be required to reimburse ONG for the filing fees and arbitration costs paid by it unless the arbitrator determines that your claim was frivolous. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this arbitration provision, ONG will pay all fees and costs that it is required by law to pay, including payment of your attorney’s fees and litigation costs if required by applicable law. In addition, if the arbitration award is greater than ONG’s last settlement offer or if ONG did not make a settlement offer, ONG will pay twice the amount of your attorney’s fees, reimburse the expenses reasonably incurred by your attorney in pursuing your claim and a $7,500 minimum recovery; provided, however, that you may not recover duplicative awards of attorney’s fees and expenses. Although under some laws ONG may have the right to an award of attorney’s fees and expenses if it prevails, ONG agrees not to seek such an award.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Both you and ONG expressly waive the right to bring a class action claim. All parties to the arbitration must be individually named. There shall be no right or authority for any claims to be arbitrated or litigated on a class action or consolidated basis or on bases involving claims brought in a representative capacity on behalf of the general public (such as a private attorney general), other recipients of gas service from ONG, or other persons similarly situated.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>You and ONG agree that where the amount at issue is a small claim within the jurisdiction of the Municipal or County Court and is an individual and not a class action claim, you or ONG may elect to proceed in that court.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Choice of Law and Venue&lt;/b> – This contract shall be construed under and shall be governed by the laws of the State of Ohio without regard to the application of its conflicts of law principles, except that the Federal Arbitration Act shall govern the arbitrability and the arbitration of all Disputes. Venue for any lawsuit brought to enforce any term or condition of this contract or to construe the terms hereof shall lie exclusively in the State of Ohio, including in a United States District Court in Ohio having jurisdiction over the case.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>ONG-0289&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>OH-CO-RS-54.4&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                confirmationcontent="[&lt;p>We are currently processing your transfer of service request. A confirmation email will be sent shortly. If there are any issues\, we will contact you to remedy them.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Once your order is completed\, you will receive your written agreement\, including your Terms and Conditions of Service\, in the mail. In addition\, your local distribution company will send you a letter confirming your Ohio Natural Gas enrollment.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Thank you for choosing Ohio Natural Gas to be your natural gas supplier.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;]"
                deltaconfirmationcontent="&lt;p>You have selected to provide us with your Delta SkyMiles account number later. When you are ready, please go to &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymiles.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com/skymiles.html&lt;/a> to enter your number to get your bonus miles.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                deltaimagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/about/delta-image.jpg"
                deltaofferterms="&lt;p>* bonus miles offer limited to qualified new customers who use 25,000 Ccf/2,500 Mcf per year or less enrolling on an eligible price plan by  using applicable promotion code. ONG service is available for eligible customers participating in the Choice program through their natural gas utility company. ONG rates do not include taxes or local utility charges. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call 1.866.466.4487, write to Ohio Natural Gas, PO Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev-ohio.macquarium.com:4502/content/onlyong.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.onlyong.com&lt;/a>. Early termination charges apply for residential fixed price plans (12-Month plan: $150/$75; 6-Month plan: $75) and commercial fixed price plans (12-Month plan:  $300/$150; 6-Month plan: $150.) 30 days of continuous active gas service with ONG required to receive  bonus miles. Cannot be combined with any other offer. You must be a SkyMiles member and provide your SkyMiles account number to ONG to participate in this program and earn miles. In addition to bonus miles, two miles will be awarded for each dollar spent for ONG supplier gas charges for monthly gas service. Miles will not be awarded for taxes or one-time charges such as late fees. SkyMiles Medallion® Members will be awarded one additional mile for eligible charges. Miles will be posted to your SkyMiles account up to 4 weeks after each monthly bill date, provided you remain in good standing in the SkyMiles program. By enrolling in this program, you are authorizing the sharing of your information with Delta for the purpose of completing your enrollment and continuing your participation in the program. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/ohioskymilesterms.html&quot;>onlyong.com/skymiles&lt;/a> for program terms and conditions. All SkyMiles program rules apply. To review the rules, please visit Membership Guide &amp;amp; Program Rules at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.delta.com/memberguide&quot;>www.delta.com/memberguide&lt;/a>. All ONG program rules, and Delta prices and SkyMiles rules, are subject to change without notice. Taxes and fees for Award Travel are the responsibility of the passenger and must be paid at the time the ticket is booked. Award Travel seats are limited and may not be available on all flights or in all markets. Delta, SkyMiles, and the Delta logo are registered service marks of Delta Air Lines, Inc. Delta is not responsible for goods or services offered by any companies participating in miles promotions. Partner offers subject to the terms and conditions of each individual offer. See individual offers for details. Offers void where prohibited by law. Other restrictions may apply. Ohio Natural Gas and Delta Air Lines, Inc. are not affiliated, and neither has any obligation or liability with respect to the products or services to be provided by the other.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                donthaveskymilesnum="Don’t have your SkyMiles Number at the Moment?"
                donthaveskymilesnumdesc="&lt;p>If you do not have your Delta SkyMiles Number with you, please call us at 1.888.466.4427 within two weeks so that we can update your account. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                footernote="&lt;p>You may rescind your enrollment without penalty within 7 business days of the postmark date of your written agreement by contacting the utility by phone or in writing. If any of the information above is not correct or you have additional questions, please call Ohio Natural Gas at 1.888.466.4427 and reference the Confirmation Number shown above.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                header="Start Earning with Delta SkyMiles"
                headercontent="&lt;h4>Welcome to Ohio Natural Gas!&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please check the account number you entered below. If it's incorrect, please go back and re-enter it.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                headerdesc="&lt;p>Switch to Ohio Natural Gas and start earning with Delta SkyMiles®. Ohio Natural Gas is excited to be a Delta SkyMiles partner and the only gas supplier in Ohio with whom you can earn miles just for paying your natural gas bill.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                howitworks="&lt;h3>How It Works&lt;/h3>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Customers will now earn TWO miles for every dollar spent on their ONG supplier natural gas charges (excluding sales tax and one-time charges)!&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>And, if you are a Delta SkyMiles® Medallion® member, Delta will award an additional mile for each dollar spent as described above!&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>It’s easy to start participating. Simply enter your ONG account and SkyMiles member information below. If you’d prefer to enroll by phone, call ONG (toll-free) at &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-888-211-8312&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1.888.466.4427&lt;/a> and mention that you would like to enroll in ONG’s Delta SkyMiles partnership program. Please have your SkyMiles account number handy when you call.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/delta-faqs.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Frequently Asked Questions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymilesterms.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Delta Program Terms &amp;amp; Conditions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.delta.com/profile/enrolllanding.action?mkcpgn=DP_ALL_DRCT_ALL_SP_150915_PRTNER17&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Join Delta Skymiles &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                iframepdffilepath="https://docs.google.com/gview?url=http://stage-ohio.macquarium.com:4505/content/dam/ohgre/termsandconditions/Ohio/OH-CO-RS-54.4.pdf&amp;embedded=true"
                offerterms="&lt;p>$25 Visa Reward Card offer is available to new residential customers enrolling online with Ohio Natural Gas between 01/02/2018 and 01/31/2018 using applicable promotion code. Customer must have continuous active service with Ohio Natural Gas for at least 60 days to be eligible to receive the Visa Reward Card. After reaching eligibility, please allow 4-6 weeks for delivery. Visa Reward Card is issued by and is property of CenterState Bank of Florida, NA pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. Cannot be combined with any other offer. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-800-970-3146&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1.888.466.44427&lt;/a>, write to Ohio Natural Gas, P.O. Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com&lt;/a>.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                pdffilepath="/content/dam/ohgre/termsandconditions/Ohio/OH-CO-RS-54.4.pdf"
                rafcontent="If a friend referred you to ONG and shared a 5-6 digit referral code, please enter it here."
                rafimagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/Visa/image01.jpg"
                rafofferheading="Earn $25 Visa Reward Cards through our Refer-a-Friend Program."
                rafoffersubheading="&lt;p>You can share this rate with your friends through our Refer-a-Friend program, and for each friend who signs up with us, you can both receive a $25 Visa Reward card.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;b>Hurry, the rate you received will only remain available through 01/31/2018.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> Click below to receive an email with information about the Refer-a-Friend program, or continue with your enrollment without participating.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                rafofferterms="&lt;p>* Subject to the Refer-a-Friend program (“RAF Program”) rules and &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/termsandconditions.html&quot;>terms and conditions&lt;/a>. Offer limited to: (i) qualified new residential/commercial customers (each a “Referee”) who use a promotion code through this RAF Program to enroll in an eligible ONG price plan (each a “RAF Referee”), and (ii) existing customers who refer one or more Referees using the RAF Program (each a “Referrer”). Referrers may earn a $25&amp;nbsp;Visa® Reward Card for each Referee who: (i) enrolls on an eligible ONG price plan, (ii) provides Referrer’s Referral Code at enrollment, and (iii) begins burning gas on an eligible ONG price plan. Referrers must: have either an active or pending account with ONG when Referee begins burning gas; authenticate their ONG account; accept the RAF Program terms and conditions; and participate by using the communication methods provided (email, Facebook, and Twitter) at &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/promo-raf.html&quot;>onlyong.com/promo-raf&lt;/a> and as specified in the RAF Program terms and conditions. RAF Referees earn a $25 Visa Reward Card by: (i) enrolling in an eligible ONG price plan, (ii) providing the RAF Program promotion code at enrollment (and may enter their Referrer’s unique Referral Code at that time), and (iii) reaching 60 days of continuous active service with ONG on such eligible price plan. Allow 4-6 weeks for delivery. Maximum award: $500 in Visa Reward Cards per person / calendar year for all ONG Visa Reward Card promotional offers. Offer valid for qualifying enrollments processed by ONG between 12/01/2017 and 06/30/2018. ONG service is available for eligible customers participating in the Choice program through their natural gas utility company. ONG rates do not include taxes or local utility charges. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call 1.888.466.4427, write to Ohio Natural Gas, PO Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong.html&quot;>www.onlyong.com&lt;/a>. RAF Referees cannot combine this offer with any other offer but may provide the Referrer’s unique Referral Code when enrolling using another ONG promotional offer. Referrers may combine this offer with their pre-existing discounts and promotions. The Visa Reward Card is issued by and is the property of CenterState Bank of Florida, NA pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. and is subject to the issuer’s terms and conditions. Reward Cards will not have cash access and can be used everywhere Visa debit cards are accepted. All trademarks noted herein are held by their respective owners. © 2018 Ohio Natural Gas. All Rights Reserved.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                reviewandauthorize="I authorize Ohio Natural Gas to be my natural gas supplier and to process with {{product.ldcDesc}} this transfer of service request to enroll with Ohio Natural Gas."
                specialoffercontent="Yes, Ohio Natural Gas may send me information about special offers from Ohio Natural Gas and its marketing partners."
                tcversion="OH-CO-RS-54.4"
                textIsRich="[true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true]"
                thankyouacceptspecialoffer="[Yes\, Ohio Natural Gas may send me information about special offers from Ohio Natural Gas and its marketing partners.]"
                thankyoureviewandauthorize="[I authorize Ohio Natural Gas to be my natural gas supplier and to process with {{product.ldcDesc}} this transfer of service request to enroll with Ohio Natural Gas.]"
                visaimagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/Visa/image01.jpg"
                visaofferheading="You are qualified to receive a  {{giftCardValue | currency:&quot;$&quot;:0}} VISA Reward Card"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-17T10:06:26.422-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
