<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-07T13:15:58.131-06:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/enrollpage"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Customer Lookup"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/enrollpage"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <enroll_customer
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-17T08:23:33.475+05:30"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-07T13:15:58.125-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/enroll-customer"
                acceptspecialoffer="Yes, Ohio Natural Gas may send me information about special offers from Ohio Natural Gas and its marketing partners."
                confirmationcontent="[&lt;p>We are currently processing your transfer of service request. A confirmation email will be sent shortly to &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>{{enrollReq.emailAddress}}&lt;/a>. If there are any issues\, we will contact you to remedy them.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Once your order is completed\, you will receive your written agreement including your Terms and Conditions of Service in the mail. In addition\, your local distribution company will send you a letter confirming your Ohio Natural Gas enrollment.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Thank you for choosing Ohio Natural Gas&amp;nbsp;to be your natural gas supplier.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;]"
                deltaconfirmationcontent="&lt;p>You have selected to provide us with your Delta Skymiles account number later. When you find your account number please go to &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymiles.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com/skymiles.html&lt;/a> to enter your number to get your bonus miles.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                deltaimagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/about/delta-image.jpg"
                deltaofferterms="&lt;p> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>PROGRAM TERMS AND CONDITIONS:&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>*You must be a SkyMiles member and provide your SkyMiles account number to ONG to participate in this program and earn miles. For monthly gas service, two miles will be awarded for each dollar spent for ONG supplier gas charges. Miles will not be awarded for taxes or one -time charges such as late fees. SkyMiles Medallion® program members will receive one additional mile from Delta for eligible charges. Miles will be posted to your SkyMiles account up to 4 weeks after each monthly bill date, provided you remain in good standing on the SkyMiles program. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymiles.html&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot; style=&quot;background-color: rgb(255,255,255);&quot;>onlyong.com/skymiles&lt;/a> for program terms and conditions. All SkyMiles program rules apply. To review the rules, please visit Membership Guide &amp;amp; Program Rules at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.delta.com/memberguide&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot; style=&quot;background-color: rgb(255,255,255);&quot;>www.delta.com/memberguide&lt;/a>. All ONG program rules, and Delta prices and SkyMiles rules, are subject to change without notice. Taxes and fees for Award Travel are the responsibility of the passenger and must be paid at the time the ticket is booked. Award Travel seats are limited and may not be available on all flights or in all markets. Delta, SkyMiles, and the Delta logo are registered service marks of Delta Air Lines, Inc. Delta is not responsible for goods or services offered by any companies participating in miles promotions. Partner offers subject to the terms and conditions of each individual offer. See individual offers for details. Offers void where prohibited by law. Other restrictions may apply. Ohio Natural Gas and Delta Air Lines, Inc. are not affiliated, and neither has any obligation or liability with respect to the products or services to be provided by the other.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>ONG customers in good standing who are on any of ONG’s published residential or commercial price plans and are also SkyMiles members are eligible to start earning miles. In order to maintain eligibility, a participant must receive continuous natural gas service from ONG. ONG reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to discontinue the program and/or modify the terms and conditions of the program at any time and without notice to any customer or other party.&lt;u>&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>*Program changes effective January 1, 2015. Due to processing time between ONG and Delta, some customers who pay their bills in late December 2014 could be rewarded under the new program structure for service prior to 2015.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                donthaveskymilesnum="Don’t have your skymiles Number at the Moment?"
                donthaveskymilesnumdesc="&lt;p>If you do not have your Delta Skymiles Number with you, you may enter it later. You have until xx/xx/xxxx to get us your Skymiles number. Instructions on how they can give it to you later should display here&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                header="You are eligible for a Bonus Offer"
                headercontent="&lt;h4>Welcome to Ohio Natural Gas!&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If you are an existing Ohio Natural Gas customer, please check the account number you entered below. If it is incorrect, please go back and re-enter.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                headerdesc="&lt;p>Switch to Ohio Natural Gas (ONG) and start earning with Delta SkyMiles®. Ohio Natural Gas is excited to be a Delta SkyMiles partner and the only Gas Supplier in Ohio with whom you can earn miles just for paying your natural gas bill.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                howitworks="&lt;h3>How It Works&lt;/h3>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Customers will now earn TWO miles for every dollar spent on their ONG supplier natural gas charges (excluding sales tax and one-time charges)!&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>And, if you are a Delta SkyMiles® Medallion® member, Delta will award an additional mile for each dollar spent as described above!&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>It’s easy to start participating. Simply enter your ONG account and SkyMiles member information below. If you’d prefer to enroll by phone, call ONG (toll-free) at &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-888-211-8312&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1-888-211-8312&lt;/a> and mention that you would like to enroll in ONG’s Delta SkyMiles partnership program. Please have your SkyMiles account number handy when you call.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/faq.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Frequently Asked Questions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; style=&quot;background-color: rgb(255,255,255);&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>Program Terms &amp;amp; Conditions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.delta.com/profile/enrolllanding.action?mkcpgn=DP_ALL_DRCT_ALL_SP_150915_PRTNER17&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Join Delta Skymiles &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                offersubheading="&lt;p>$25 Visa Reward Card offer is available to new residential customers enrolling online with Ohio Natural Gas between 10/1/2017 and 10/31/2017 using applicable promotion code. Customer must have continuous active service with Ohio Natural Gas for at least 60 days to be eligible to receive the Visa Reward Card. After reaching eligibility, please allow 4-6 weeks for delivery. Visa Reward Card is issued by and is property of CenterState Bank of Florida, NA pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. Cannot be combined with any other offer. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-800-970-3146&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1-800-970-3146&lt;/a>, write to Ohio Natural Gas, P.O. Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev-ohio.macquarium.com:4502/content/onlyong.html&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>onlyong.com&lt;/a>.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                offerterms="&lt;p>$25 Visa Reward Card offer is available to new residential customers enrolling online with Ohio Natural Gas between 10/1/2017 and 10/31/2017 using applicable promotion code. Customer must have continuous active service with Ohio Natural Gas for at least 60 days to be eligible to receive the Visa Reward Card. After reaching eligibility, please allow 4-6 weeks for delivery. Visa Reward Card is issued by and is property of CenterState Bank of Florida, NA pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. Cannot be combined with any other offer. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-800-970-3146&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1-800-970-3146&lt;/a>, write to Ohio Natural Gas, P.O. Box 14657, Cleveland, OH 44114, or visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong.html&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>onlyong.com&lt;/a>.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                pdffilepath="/content/dam/ohgre/termsandconditions/Ohio/OH-CO-RS-54.4.pdf"
                rafcontent="If a friend referred you to ONG and shared a 5-6 digit referral code, please enter it here."
                rafimagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/Visa/image01.jpg"
                rafofferheading="Want to earn $25 Visa Reward Cards?"
                rafoffersubheading="&lt;p>You can share this rate with your friends through our Refer-a-Friend program, and for each friend who signs up with us, you’ll both receive a $25 Visa Reward Card.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> &lt;b>Hurry, the rate you received will only remain available through 10-31-2017.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> Click below to receive an email with information about the Refer-a-Friend program, or continue with your enrollment without participating.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                rafofferterms="&lt;p>* Subject to the Refer-a-Friend program (“RAF Program”) rules and terms and conditions available at &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/refer-a-friend.html&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>onlyong.com/refer&lt;/a>. Existing ONG customers who refer one or more new customers to ONG using the RAF Program(each, a “Referrer”) may earn a $25 Visa® Reward Card for each new customer who: (i) enrolls on an eligible ONG price plan, (ii) provides Referrer’s Referral Code at enrollment, and (iii) begins burning gas on an eligible ONG price plan. Referrers must: have either an active or pending account with ONG when Referee begins burning gas; authenticate their ONG account and accept the RAF Program terms and conditions; and participate by using the communication methods provided (email, Facebook, and Twitter) at &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/refer-a-friend.html&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>onlyong.com/refer&lt;/a> and as specified in the RAF Program terms and conditions. Allow 4-6 weeks for delivery. Maximum award: $500 in Visa Reward Cards per person/calendar year for all ONG Visa Reward Card promotional offers. Offer valid for qualifying enrollments processed by ONG between 9/1/2017 and 4/30/2018. Referrers may combine this offer with their pre-existing discounts and promotions. The Visa Reward Card is issued by and is the property of Center State Bank of Florida, NA pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. and is subject to the issuer’s terms and conditions. Reward Cards will not have cash access and can be used everywhere Visa debit cards are accepted. All trademarks noted herein are held by their respective owners. Qualified new residential/commercial customers (“Referees”) shall receive ONG’s lowest available fixed price rate or the variable rate at the time of the Referee’s enrollment by enrolling in an eligible ONG price plan and providing the applicable RAF Program promotion code in the Referee offer at &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/refer-a-friend.html&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>onlyong.com/refer&lt;/a> at the time of their enrollment.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                reviewandauthorize="I authorize Ohio Natural Gas to be my natural gas supplier and to process with Columbia Gas of ohio this transfer of service request to enroll with Ohio Natural Gas."
                specialoffercontent="Yes, Ohio Natural Gas may send me information about special offers from Ohio Natural Gas and its marketing partners."
                textIsRich="[true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true]"
                thankyouacceptspecialoffer="[Yes\, Ohio Natural Gas may send me information about special offers from Ohio Natural Gas and its marketing partners.]"
                thankyoureviewandauthorize="[I authorize Ohio Natural Gas to be my natural gas supplier and to process with this transfer of service request to enroll with Ohio Natural Gas.]"
                visaimagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/Visa/image01.jpg"
                visaofferheading="Enroll online for a $25 VISA Reward Card"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-17T10:06:26.422-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
