<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-17T15:31:01.702-06:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2018-01-17T15:31:06.004-06:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/mainpage"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Delta SignUp"
        jcr:uuid="3173cfca-27a9-472b-9cff-abe6e4a58b74"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/mainpage"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <staticherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-29T16:09:56.194-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-12-13T21:52:53.112-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/staticherobanner"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/delta-image.jpg"
                title="Earn miles just for paying your gas bill!*"/>
            <delta_signup_content
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-29T16:10:02.335-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-17T15:31:01.697-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/delta-signup-content"
                confirmationpageheader="Success!"
                confirmationpagesubhead="You are now enrolled in Grand Rapids Energy's Delta SkyMiles program, where you can earn miles just for paying your gas bill!"
                deltaformheading="Delta SkyMiles Member Information"
                deltapromocode="DELTA25"
                fineprinttext="&lt;p>* You must be a SkyMiles member and provide your SkyMiles account number to GRE to participate in this program and earn miles. For monthly gas service, two miles will be awarded for each dollar spent for GRE supplier gas charges. Miles will not be awarded for taxes or one-time charges such as late fees for any plan. SkyMiles Medallion® members will receive one additional mile for eligible charges. Miles will be posted to your SkyMiles account (i) for customers in the DTE Gas Company service territory, up to 4 weeks after each monthly bill date or (ii) for customers in the Consumers Energy service territory, up to 6 weeks after each monthly bill due date, provided in each case you remain in good standing in the SkyMiles program. By enrolling in this program, you are authorizing the sharing of your information with Delta for the purpose of completing your enrollment and continuing your participation in the program. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev-ohio.macquarium.com:4502/content/gre/skymilesterms.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.grandrapidsenergy.com/skymiles&lt;/a> for program terms and conditions. All SkyMiles program rules apply. To review the rules, please visit Membership Guide &amp;amp; Program Rules at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.delta.com/content/www/en_US/skymiles/program-resources/program-rules.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.delta.com/memberguide&lt;/a>. All GRE program rules, and Delta prices and SkyMiles rules, are subject to change without notice. Taxes and fees for Award Travel are the responsibility of the passenger and must be paid at the time the ticket is booked. Award Travel seats are limited and may not be available on all flights or in all markets. Delta, SkyMiles, and the Delta logo are registered service marks of Delta Air Lines, Inc. Delta is not responsible for goods or services offered by any companies participating in miles promotions. Partner offers subject to the terms and conditions of each individual offer. See individual offers for details. Offers void where prohibited by law. Other restrictions may apply. Grand Rapids Energy and Delta Air Lines, Inc. are not affiliated, and neither has any obligation or liability with respect to the products or services to be provided by the other. GRE customers in good standing who are on any of GRE’s published residential or commercial price plans and are also SkyMiles members are eligible to start earning miles.  In order to maintain eligibility, a participant must receive continuous natural gas service from GRE. GRE reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to discontinue the program and/or modify the terms and conditions of the program at any time and without notice to any customer or other party.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                formheader="Grand Rapids Energy Account Information"
                header="&lt;h4>It’s easy to start participating.&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Simply enter your GRE account and SkyMiles member information below. If you’d prefer to enroll by phone, call GRE toll-free at &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-800-841-1541&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1.800.841.1541&lt;/a> and mention that you would like to enroll in GRE’s Delta SkyMiles program. Please have your SkyMiles account number handy when you call.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/card_plans.jpg"
                infoheader="Grand Rapids Energy Account Information"
                promotionpath="/content/gre/promo_landing"
                sidecontent="&lt;h4>Start Earning Miles with Delta SkyMiles®.&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Grand Rapids Energy is excited to be a Delta SkyMiles partner and the only alternative gas supplier in Michigan with whom you can earn miles from Delta just for paying your natural gas bill.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h4>How it works:&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Customers will now earn TWO miles for every dollar spent on their GRE supplier natural gas charges (excluding sales tax and one-time charges)!*&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>And, if you are a Delta SkyMiles® Medallion® member, Delta will award an additional mile for each dollar spent as described above!&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/gre/delta-faqs.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Frequently Asked Questions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;http://dev-ohio.macquarium.com:4502/content/gre/skymilesterms.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Terms and Conditions&amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                textIsRich="[true,true,true]"
                viewplansheader="Not a Grand Rapids Energy customer?"
                viewplanssubhead="Want to sign up with Grand Rapids Energy to take advantage of this offer?"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-01T22:31:06.747-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
