<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-03-06T15:33:49.135-06:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2018-03-06T15:33:53.347-06:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/mainpage"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Delta SignUp"
        jcr:uuid="f29a0303-7c4b-4acb-ba65-5eeb7b271095"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/mainpage"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <staticherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-29T16:09:56.194-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-17T16:33:49.238-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/staticherobanner"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/delta-image.jpg"
                title="Earn miles just for paying your gas bill!*"/>
            <delta_signup_content
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-29T16:10:02.335-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-03-06T15:33:49.129-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/delta-signup-content"
                confirmationpageheader="Thank you for considering Ohio Natural Gas."
                confirmationpagesubhead="Your information has been submitted successfully!"
                deltaformheading="Delta SkyMiles Member Information"
                deltapromocode="DELTA25"
                fineprinttext="&lt;p>* You must be a SkyMiles Member and provide your SkyMiles account number to ONG to participate in this program and earn miles. In addition to bonus miles, two miles&amp;nbsp;will be awarded for each dollar spent for ONG supplier gas charges for monthly gas service. Miles will not be awarded for taxes or one-time charges such as late fees. SkyMiles Medallion® Members will be awarded one additional&amp;nbsp;mile for eligible charges. Miles will be posted to your SkyMiles account up to 4 weeks after each monthly bill date, provided you remain in good standing in the SkyMiles program. By enrolling&amp;nbsp;in this program, you are authorizing the sharing of your information with Delta for the purpose of completing your enrollment and continuing your participation in the program. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymilesterms.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>onlyong.com/skymiles&lt;/a> for program terms&amp;nbsp;and conditions. All SkyMiles program rules apply. To review the rules, please visit Membership Guide &amp;amp; Program Rules at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.delta.com/memberguide&quot;>www.delta.com/memberguide&lt;/a>. All ONG program rules, and Delta prices and SkyMiles rules, are subject&amp;nbsp;to change without notice. Taxes and fees for Award Travel are the responsibility of the passenger and must be paid at the time the ticket is booked. Award Travel seats are limited and may not be available on all flights or in all&amp;nbsp;markets. Delta, SkyMiles, and the Delta logo are registered service marks of Delta Air Lines, Inc. Delta is not responsible for goods or services offered by any companies participating in miles promotions. Partner offers subject&amp;nbsp;to the terms and conditions of each individual offer. See individual offers for details. Offers void where prohibited by law. Other restrictions may apply. Ohio Natural Gas and Delta Air Lines, Inc. are not affiliated, and neither&amp;nbsp;has any obligation or liability with respect to the products or services to be provided by the other.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                formheader="Ohio Natural Gas Account Information"
                header="&lt;h4>It’s easy to start participating.&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;>Simply enter your ONG account and SkyMiles Member information below. If you’d prefer to enroll by phone, call ONG toll-free at &lt;a href=&quot;tel:1-888-466-4427&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>1.888.466.4427&lt;/a> and mention that you would like to enroll in ONG’s Delta SkyMiles&amp;nbsp;program. Please have your SkyMiles account number handy when you call.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/card_plans.jpg"
                infoheader="Ohio Natural Gas Account Information"
                promotionpath="/content/onlyong/promo_landing"
                sidecontent="&lt;h4>Start Earning Miles with Delta SkyMiles®.&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Ohio Natural Gas(ONG) is excited to be a Delta SkyMiles partner and the only natural gas supplier in Ohio with whom you can earn miles from Delta just for paying your natural gas bill.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h4>How it works:&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Customers will&amp;nbsp;earn TWO miles for every dollar spent on their ONG supplier natural gas charges (excluding sales tax and one-time charges)!*&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>And, if you are a Delta SkyMiles® Medallion® Member, Delta will award an additional mile for each dollar spent as described above!&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/delta-faqs.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Frequently Asked Questions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/onlyong/skymilesterms.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Program&amp;nbsp;Terms &amp;amp; Conditions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                textIsRich="[true,true,true]"
                viewplansheader="Not an Ohio Natural Gas Customer?"
                viewplanssubhead="Not yet a customer, but want to sign up with Ohio Natural Gas to take advantage of this offer?"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-01T22:31:06.747-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
