<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-02-08T11:02:04.299-06:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2018-02-08T11:02:08.277-06:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="penny"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/promolandingwithoutnav"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Delta Promotion"
        jcr:uuid="f272b662-2559-4a3d-8ec5-6f36f7b98a67"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/promolandingwithoutnavpage"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <promoherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-07-27T08:23:50.174+05:30"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-02-06T10:33:55.293-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/promoherobanner"
                description="\{{DELTAMILES}} BONUS MILES for enrolling + earn miles for every dollar you spend on your gas bill.*"
                displaylogo="true"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/delta-image.jpg"
                promocode="delta25"
                promoexpmsg="Start Earning! Offer ends  {{currentMonthLastDay}}."
                textIsRich="true"
                title="Fuel for Your Next Getaway"/>
            <promotioncontent
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-07-27T10:17:02.253+05:30"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2018-02-08T11:02:04.295-06:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="penny"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/promotioncontent"
                fineprinttext="&lt;p>*Rates and Price Plans effective from {{currentMonthFirstDay}}&amp;nbsp; to {{currentMonthLastDay}}. Price offers are available to new qualified residential customers enrolling with Grand Rapids Energy by {{EXPIRATIONDATE}} using applicable promotion code.&amp;nbsp;GRE service is available for eligible customers participating in the Gas Customer Choice program through their natural gas utility company. GRE rates do not include taxes or local utility charges. For more information regarding terms and conditions, call 1.800.841.1541, write to Grand Rapids Energy, 400 Renaissance Center, Ste. 2600, Detroit, MI 48243 or visit this site.&amp;nbsp;Early Termination Charges apply for residential fixed price plans (12-Month plan: $50/$25, 6-Month plan: $25). {{DELTAMILES}}&amp;nbsp;bonus miles offer limited to qualified new residential customers who enroll on an eligible price plan by {{EXPIRATIONDATE}} using applicable promotion code. 30 days of continuous active gas service with GRE required to receive {{DELTAMILES}}&amp;nbsp;bonus miles. Cannot be combined with any other offer. You must be a SkyMiles member and provide your SkyMiles account number to GRE to participate in this program and earn miles. For monthly gas service, two miles will be awarded for each dollar spent for GRE supplier gas charges. Miles will not be awarded for taxes or one-time charges such as late fees for any plan. SkyMiles Medallion® members will receive one additional mile for eligible charges. Miles will be posted to your SkyMiles account (i) for customers in the DTE Gas Company service territory, up to 4 weeks after each monthly bill date or (ii) for customers in the Consumers Energy service territory, up to 6 weeks after each monthly bill due date, provided in each case you remain in good standing in the SkyMiles program. By enrolling in this program, you are authorizing the sharing of your information with Delta for the purpose of completing your enrollment and continuing your participation in the program. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev-ohio.macquarium.com:4502/content/gre/skymiles.html&quot; target=&quot;Target&quot;>www.grandrapidsenergy.com/skymiles&lt;/a> for program terms and conditions. All SkyMiles program rules apply. To review the rules, please visit Membership Guide &amp;amp; Program Rules at www.delta.com/memberguide. All GRE program rules, and Delta prices and SkyMiles rules, are subject to change without notice. Taxes and fees for Award Travel are the responsibility of the passenger and must be paid at the time the ticket is booked. Award Travel seats are limited and may not be available on all flights or in all markets. Delta, SkyMiles, and the Delta logo are registered service marks of Delta Air Lines, Inc. Delta is not responsible for goods or services offered by any companies participating in miles promotions. Partner offers subject to the terms and conditions of each individual offer. See individual offers for details. Offers void where prohibited by law. Other restrictions may apply. Grand Rapids Energy and Delta Air Lines, Inc. are not affiliated, and neither has any obligation or liability with respect to the products or services to be provided by the other. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                heading="Choose from one of our plans to get started right away!"
                promoheadingline1="Get started by selecting your utility"
                text="&lt;h4>Get {{DELTAMILES}} bonus miles for signing up on a GRE fixed price plan, using applicable promo code, PLUS earn TWO miles for every dollar spent on your GRE supplier natural gas charges.*&lt;/h4>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>And, if you are a SkyMiles Medallion® member, earn an additional mile for a total of THREE miles for each eligible dollar spent.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Bonus miles offer ends &amp;nbsp;{{currentMonthLastDay}}.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h5>Easy Sign Up&lt;/h5>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul style=&quot;list-style-position: inside;&quot;>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Switching is easy! One call to us and we&amp;#39;ll handle all the details.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>There will be no service interruption.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Our experts ensure a seamless transition.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Your utility will continue to deliver your gas, send you one monthly bill and respond to service calls.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Limited to qualified new customers enrolled on an eligible price plan.*&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Already a GRE customer?&amp;nbsp;Visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/content/gre/skymiles.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.grandrapidsenergy.com/skymiles&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;to learn how you can earn miles.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/gre/delta-faqs.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Frequently Asked Questions &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/gre/skymilesterms.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Program Terms and Conditions&amp;nbsp;&amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a title=&quot;Join Delta&quot; href=&quot;https://www.delta.com/profile/enrolllanding.action?mkcpgn=DP_ALL_DRCT_ALL_SP_150915_PRTNER17&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Join Delta SkyMiles &amp;gt;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                textIsRich="[true,true,true]"/>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-01T19:13:25.412+05:30"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
