<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-30T13:53:53.708-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="rebecka.wilson"
        cq:template="/apps/ohgre/templates/helppage"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="WHAT IS CHOICE?"
        sling:resourceType="/apps/ohgre/components/structure/helppage">
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
            <staticherobanner
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-03T15:30:38.679-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-03T15:39:54.935-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/staticherobanner"
                description="It means you have the power to choose your natural gas supplier, which means you could get a lower rate!"
                imagepath="/content/dam/ohgre/home/hero-image.jpg"
                title="What is Choice?"/>
            <wiccontent
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-03T16:40:22.135-04:00"
                jcr:createdBy="admin"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-30T13:53:53.704-05:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="rebecka.wilson"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="ohgre/components/wiccontent"
                description="&lt;p>So why choose a higher rate for natural gas when you could get the same natural gas at a&amp;nbsp;&lt;b style=&quot;font-size: 0.8125rem;&quot;>lower rate?&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Luckily for you, this is possible because in Ohio you can choose your natural gas supplier!&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Huh? What does that mean exactly?&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;It means you can purchase natural gas from a company (hint hint, Ohio Natural Gas) who may be offering a lower price than your current utility. Compare rates with Ohio Natural Gas and go with the lowest to save big on your natural gas bill!&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Why is ONG so great?&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;We offer flexible plan options, exceptional customer service and outstanding perks.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Plus, when you lock in your natural gas price for the next 6 or 12 months with ONG you can avoid price spikes and fluctuations. You don’t have this option with your regulated utility company, but you do with us! And there are no sign-up fees.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Is switching to ONG difficult?&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Not a bit. We handle all the details with NO interruption to your service. Switch in just 3 easy steps.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                heading="Would you choose a $10 car wash when you couls get the EXACT same car wash for $5?"
                leftboxdescription="&lt;p>So why choose a higher rate for natural gas when you could get the same natural gas at a&amp;nbsp;&lt;b>lower rate?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Luckily for you, this is possible because in Ohio you can &lt;i>choose&lt;/i> your natural gas supplier!&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What does that mean exactly?&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;It means you can purchase natural gas from a company (hint hint, Grand Rapids Energy®) who may be offering a lower natural gas price than your current price. Compare rates with Grand Rapids Energy® and go with the lowest to save on your natural gas bill!&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Why is GRE so great?&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;We offer flexible plan options, exceptional customer service and outstanding perks.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Plus, when you lock in your natural gas price for the next 6 or 12 months with GRE you can avoid price spikes and fluctuations. &lt;b>You don’t have this option with your regulated utility company, but you do with us!&lt;/b> And there are no sign-up fees.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Is switching to GRE difficult?&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Not a bit.&amp;nbsp;We handle all the details with NO interruption to your service. Switch in just 3 easy steps.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Have questions? Check out our FAQ or call 1-800-841-1541 to speak with one of our customer service representatives.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>After you switch, think about this little Zen nugget:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;When we’re able to choose where we purchase our natural gas from, we feel more in control over our expenses and therefore a greater sense of happiness. So choosing GRE is choosing happiness, it’s science!*&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>*It’s not really science.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                leftboxheading="Would you choose a $10 car wash when you could get the EXACT same car wash for $5?"
                note="Note: Your gas utility will continue to distribute gas to your location, send you your bill, check for gas leaks and respond to emergencies."
                rightbottomboxtext="&lt;p>&lt;b>Have Questions?&lt;/b>&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;Check out our &lt;a title=&quot;none&quot; href=&quot;http://localhost:4502/editor.html/content/onlyong/what_is_choice.html#&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>FAQ&lt;/a> or call &lt;b>1-888-466-4427&lt;/b> to speak with one of our customer service representatives.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                rightsidepoint1="Select Your Current Gas Utility – we serve customers enrolled in DTE Gas Company and Consumers Energy choice programs."
                rightsidepoint2="Let us know if the property Commercial or Residential"
                rightsidepoint3="Choose from one of our great rate plans and complete the sign up process right here and now!"
                righttopheading="Switch from your utility to ONG in just 3 easy steps."
                textIsRich="[true,true]"/>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
